Is it okay to be quick?
早くていい?
Go to sleep now.
今寝るんじゃ
It's cute.
かわいいね
Where are you from?
どこから来たの?
Home.
おうち
Let's play a lot.
いっぱい遊ぼう
いっぱい遊ぼうね
It's cute.
かわいいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
cute
かわいい
hey.
ね
Do you want to eat sweets?
お 菓子食べる?
It's cute.
かわいいね
Let's be careful.
気をつけよう
Are you wearing adult-like pants like this?
こんな大人っぽいパンツ履いてるの?
So, make sure to wear your shoes properly.
じゃあ、しっかり履いてね
Children these days.
最近の子は
How do you feel like that?
そんな感じどうすんの?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I have to go home.
帰りなきゃね
I like it at home.
おうちに好きだし
I love you at home and do it properly.
おうちに好きだし、ちゃんと
amazing.
すごい
You have a naughty face.
えっちゃな顔してるね
Are you wearing this all over your head?
こんな頭いっぱい履いてるの?
What should I do?
どうすんの?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Feeling good, right?
気 持 ちいいでしょ?
I'll show it to you soon.
早く見せてから
Come on.
おいけ
Do you want to look behind you?
後ろ見たいの?
Okay.
いいよ
Shall we watch it soon?
早く見ちゃおうか
It's so cute.
すごいかわいいね
Aunt
おば
Are you sleeping?
あ い寝てる?
Is grandma sleeping?
おばあい寝てる?
Shut up a little.
ちょっとしめて
Push it up.
上にしめて
Show me!
見せてよっ
mosquito.
か
Are you sleeping?
寝 てる?
amazing.
すごい
do your best.
頑張って
It's tough.
きついね